{
  "easyquestions": [
    {
      "question": "What is 12 ÷ 4?",
      "answer1": "3",
      "answer2": "4",
      "correct": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 15 ÷ 3?",
      "answer1": "5",
      "answer2": "6",
      "correct": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 20 ÷ 5?",
      "answer1": "4",
      "answer2": "5",
      "correct": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 18 ÷ 2?",
      "answer1": "9",
      "answer2": "8",
      "correct": "9"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 8 ÷ 2?",
      "answer1": "4",
      "answer2": "5",
      "correct": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 9 ÷ 3?",
      "answer1": "3",
      "answer2": "6",
      "correct": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 16 ÷ 4?",
      "answer1": "4",
      "answer2": "5",
      "correct": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 14 ÷ 2?",
      "answer1": "7",
      "answer2": "6",
      "correct": "7"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 10 ÷ 5?",
      "answer1": "2",
      "answer2": "5",
      "correct": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 24 ÷ 6?",
      "answer1": "4",
      "answer2": "5",
      "correct": "4"
    }
  ]
}
